is. We must act so that Russia is
aware that we remember that we have not
indulgence and we fight for international law
and basic human justice and
who will prevail.
that kind of crime must not go
unpunished. Just a few days ago
so the city of Tenopil was hit by one
widespread attack. and Belgian
on behalf of the senate, we uh want the victims in
commemoration and give expression to our
unfailing support for those who are now defending
eh their country, those displaced and those
deprived of everything. The Russian attack
on Ukraine is more than just a geopolitical one
challenge. It is a deep and comprehensive
challenge for the security of all of Europe.